The dead of night changed the lives of many... and ended the lives of some.
Dead of Night is a horror film directed by Bob Clark.
A young soldier who was thought to be killed in Vietnam returns home and
exhibits disturbing behavior, much to the confusion of his family.
Charles Brooks, played by John Marley.
Christine Brooks, played by Lynn Carlin.
Andy Brooks, played by Richard Backus.
Dr. Philip Allman, played by Henderson Forsythe.
Cathy Brooks, played by Anya Ormsby.
Joanne, played by Jane Daly.
Deathdream (originally released as Dead of Night) is a 1974 horror film directed and produced by Bob
Clark, written by Alan Ormsby, and starring Richard Backus, John Marley, and Lynn Carlin.
Inspired by the W.
Jacobs short story "The Monkey's Paw", the film is about young American soldier Andy Brooks (Backus) who
returns home after seemingly being killed in Vietnam, only now as an undead, vampiric creature.
The film explores themes of vietnam veteran, suicide,
vampire, cemetery, drive-in theater.
The tone is dark.